Well, are you in like or are you in love?
How do you know if you love him?
This is Dr. Paul, author of Boomer Girls: A Boomer Woman's Guide to Men and Dating and host of Ask Dr. Paul.
Now ladies, number one, you don't ask your girlfriends, am I in love with him?
Bad idea.
It has to come from within.
Okay? And you have to make that definition; I started with, are you in like or are you in love; identify that.
Are you in like?
Are you in love with love?
Or are you in love with him?
Oftentimes, we are in love with love itself.
It's so nice, it's springtime, or whatever.
And we decide that we're going to be in love.
Well, that's nice, but it doesn't work.
You need to define where your love is.
If you are in love with him, you will feel it intrinsically.
You are going to feel it from the inside.
And if you're in love with him, you're going to make it very easy for yourself by not asking your friends.
You have to ask yourself.
And I know this may sound strange, but please listen.
Go to the mirror, one of Dr. Paul's recommendations and one of Dr. Paul's remedies.
Look at yourself in the mirror.
Look right into your eyes, and you ask yourself the question, am I in love with him?
When you do that, an interesting thing happens.
You can't lie to yourself.
And you will tell yourself the truth, because only you know what the truth is.
And when you look at your image and you look into your own eyes and you ask yourself that question, you are going to know the answer.
And that is the recommendation I make.
That is how to do it.
And that goes for so many things.
But it especially goes for a love interest.
And you watch.
And one thing you might want to watch too, watch the pupils of your eyes.
See if they open or see if they close.
A little body language there on your own behalf.
This is Dr. Paul.
May your fantasies of today be your realties of tomorrow.